Jeffrey Headen

President & CEO

Greenville, SC 29605 jeffreyheaden8_9x9@indeedemail.com 864-382-8371

Demonstrated the ability to complete tasks accurately despite interruptions and competing demands. Vice President with management experience and exceptional people skills. Versed in Leadership and Management. Desires a challenging role as a President.

Articulate Vice President driven to succeed. Strategic planning and client relationship management expert.

#readytowork

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

President & CEO

Headen Investments & Acquisitions Co., Inc - Philadelphia, PA August 2006 to Present

- Monitored multiple databases to keep track of all company inventory.
- Increased sales by 17% over a two-year period.
- Conducted analysis to address Shrink which led to profitability.
- Provided onsite training.
- Successfully led key projects which resulted in constant growth.
- Reviewed and provided comments on the adequacy of documents and took necessary steps to cure any deficiencies.
- Delivered an exceptional level of service to each customer by listening to concerns and answering questions.

Vice President Operations

Citizens Financial Mortgages Inc - Huntingdon Valley, PA July 2006 to January 2007

- Collaborated with support personnel to affect satisfactory and timely solutions to diverse issues.
- Empowered staff members to contribute to the continuous improvement, quality and growth of the company.
- Built financial model for new business unit.
- Served as mentor to junior team members.
- Initiated program that standardized employee training and led to increase in customer satisfaction by 12%.
- Implemented effective customer service procedures to encourage positive feedback.
- Utilized strategic and forward-thinking business techniques to maximize turnover.

President

JL. RH. Enterprises Inc - Hillside, NJ

February 1995 to December 2005

- Managed the company's key account to ensure ongoing profitability of projects and superior customer satisfaction.
- Consistently exceeded sales goals through up-selling and cross-selling within the existing client base as well as attracting new business.
- Oversaw technological improvements that reduced waste and business bottlenecks.
- Increased the organization's exposure to the Business Brokering industry to grow sales profitability.
- Led the startup and opening of JL RH. Enterprises Inc., and provided business development, creation of operational procedures and workflow planning.
- Recruited, hired and trained 400 employees on operations and performance expectations.
- Developed and maintained strong business relationships between departments.
- Created program to promote new managers from within, leading to a cohesive leadership structure.

Education

MBA in Global Leadership, Business Administration, Management

Colorado Technical University - Colorado Springs, CO September 2016 to June 2018

Bachelor of Science in Leadership, Business Administration, Management

Colorado Technical University - Colorado Springs, CO

December 2014 to August 2016

Associate of Science in Leadership, Business Administration, Management

Colorado Technical University - Colorado Springs, CO

September 2010 to November 2012

Six Sigma Certification in Lean Six Sigma, Green Belt Six Sigma

Villanova University - Villanova, PA

August 2008 to September 2010

Skills

- TRAINING (10+ years)
- CHANGE MANAGEMENT (8 years)
- OPERATIONS (10+ years)
- OPERATIONS MANAGEMENT (10+ years)
- CONTRACT NEGOTIATION (10+ years)

Additional Information

Skills

- Contract auditing
- Operations management
- · Excellent communication
- · Financial records and processing

- Contract negotiation/review/drafting
- Proficiency in Leadership
- Results-oriented
- Microsoft Office
- Training and development
- Client-focused
- Change management
- Computer proficient
- Reports generation and analysis